so I just wanted to update you all on my
last 24 hours I don't even know what
happened during the day yesterday I feel
like other amazing stuff other amazing
things I'm watching the video between
Eric and I that isn't available but he's
gonna edit part of it so that we can
make it available cuz I think during
part of it although I'm swearing and
angry and just like frustrated for most
of the entire conversation and just pre
watching it like old me would have had
so much social anxiety that I showed up
like that for for 2 hours 3 hours but it
was in and out and I I don't cuz I'm
like thank God I have this guy in my
life who allows me to show up like that
who like it was such a different
conversation with the two of us you know
make a group versus when there's a bunch
of people and I know like our
relationship is is strong enough that I
even was like thank you for being there
he's like no need to thank me this is
it's like what we're doing and now he's
gonna add it part of the video so that
that I couldn't put it on my channel for
like this is what the global tech
cooperative can give us what the
solutions cooperative can give us and
he's skeptical about the feasibility of
it and so during the conversation we I
think I'm convincing him more and more
but maybe not that's not the point the
point is is to be able to articulate it
then there is this woman on Facebook who
kept trying to friend me but her
Facebook profile isn't there's no
picture she's got no history of like I'm
if we have no friends in common so I
deleted her friend request twice and
then she messaged me I think she
messaged me before the next friend
request I just didn't see it and wow I'm
ever glad she did because she was like I
love your YouTube channel something
along those lines but she put me in
touch with radish org which I will link
in the description and this group of
people there dude they're working on
collective intelligence
Jamin one of the founders or the founder
does a 24 hour zoom session every Friday
so from 6:00 a.m. Pacific Standard Time
to 6:00 a.m. Saturday morning Pacific
Standard
I'm he is on although tonight he's gonna
be taking a young and the person just
message me I can't read it right now but
the the synchronicity that happened
speed on that call this morning I woke
up specifically to be on that I'm like
oh tomorrow morning at 6:00 a.m. I'll
get up and go on that call and watching
them with their vision and then the guy
that was just on who's doing this um
social media which what I would call it
he called it something different social
media platform that is just exactly what
the world needs and I'm gonna reach out
to him later I'm having this
conversation with another person in game
B who I don't think we've ever connected
on video video briefly because he was he
was in the Omega Tuesday group this this
time that's why he reached out to have a
conversation he is somebody who gets the
big picture of like what a tech
cooperative can do and so we're gonna
have a conversation later after today's
what usually is the board meeting on
Fridays today is an idea cafe for the
meta project on trust and that's in less
than an hour so I'm just coming on to
update my last 24 hours of like we can't
even contact with the coronavirus but
like that's not even a blip on the radar
I met this amazing woman on Facebook who
put me in touch with the radish org who
put me in touch with the new map which
is gonna probably be called something
different and oh oh ma p and just the
pieces are coming together this is why
this channel exists because I wouldn't
be able to at the ends of this be like
and here's how we got here like every
day there's these amazing things
happening these people coming in and
like they're just exactly what you need
in that moment I didn't think I need it
at 24 hour zoom call to jump into on
Fridays in fact if anything I really
don't need not another amazing group of
humans trying to save the world how do I
keep it all straight you know you're
like one piece of it
one little hold on and you take it with
you but I'm gonna link radish org in the
description I'm gonna do a video next
week on like the four world-changing
projects that I I'm part of in some
small way either just knowing about them
and knowing the person who does them or
I can then there's like all these other
amazing projects that themselves aren't
like overarching world-changing but they
are absolutely world-changing like cubes
bond and a common planet with with Remzi
who his is an overarching but like his
those pieces of it but I'm like yes
let's have that and I get to encounter
all of these people who have amazing
ideas and are willing to have
conversations about those ideas because
that's my job having a video chat
expecially if we can record and it can
be put up for everyone to see as to like
what is your idea and how do we
implement it and what is the the
blockage why isn't it in the world yet
and then let's solve all of those
problems together I just when I do this
video next week like if you aren't
living in hope right now if you're
living in despair over the state of the
world get involved in any of the
projects I talked about radishes or game
be the transition org and work together
tech together tech art
now this plug ours as well that there
are world changers coming together and
creating the technology and the
community that everyone is welcome to
join and I am just so grateful and
excited thank you